It's Halloween soon so today I'm going to show you three Halloween costumes
from Wodinka and I mean we're talking about high quality costumes which you
can wear for more than a year and not only Halloween but I got something red I
got something black PVC and yes I'm filming in my living room for a change
and yes this is my pole fitness pole in my kitchen because that's the only place
I have enough space here in my flat. Anyway I'm going to start with the first
outfit. It's going to be this red not much of fabric outfit so to say and I
think I'll pair it with my red PVC overknees. I'm presenting you the Devil May Cry
cry winged bodysuit from badenka it's a chippy set the bodysuit and the cape and i added some
horns because hello devil and i think it is a really cool thing to have to cape so i'm not
feeling too naked but yeah it is not an outdoor costume i would say it's an indoor costume because
on Halloween it's going to be cold outside and you may not want to wear this except if you're
living somewhere south. The fabric is super soft so it's not scratchy at all as you may
experience from some of these sheer fabrics. You can also wear it of course without the cape.
We have some snap buttons here but it's just a pull over the arms. As I said I paired it with
some red ovany boots so I think all in all this is a cool and stylish Halloween
costume or for your next model party or whenever you may want to play little
devil I'm wearing size small and I could fit my c2d cup into the bodysuit but
it's also perfect for cups a and B and I think it just looks really fun also from
behind and the fabric itself is really stretchy so the bodysuit when I unpacked
it I was like oh am I going to fit into it thanks wise but yeah it's super super
stretchy and also really comfortable for the next outfit I have a set and part of
this set that's going to be this little cat mask so maybe you know what will
come next. See you in a sec. Second outfit is the cat's meow. It's a vinyl set. We have the romper,
we have the arm warmers here and above the romper have a look at the seams. See they're really nice.
so it makes a nice body shape with all the panels and the cut and we also have the mask
with the cute little cat ears and I'm going to put that on now. There is a rubber band in the mask
you can put your ponytail through.
Right here.
That's a really handy gimmick and also if you want to wear it for the whole night.
I have to say the four-way stretch while in fabric is really really comfy.
So wearing a mask is not a problem, wearing a garampa is not a problem.
I think that makes a really good outfit for Halloween. You can also spice it up
with some accessories for example. Fun fact about vinyl and PVC it sticks to
the pole so it's really cool to wear it for pole because you stick to it.
It is handy to have the pole in the videos.
I don't know.
As you can see I move around in this romper a lot because it is so stretchy.
So I think this is a really cool outfit to spend the night in the Halloween night or
any other costume party night.
If it gets too cold you can put a jacket on top of it and have fun.
thing is there is no sip in the crotch so you have to undress every time you go to the bathroom.
But Inca makes not only Halloween costumes but also outfits for rave parties and they're
especially known for their printed jumpsuits and this is going to be my third outfit which you'll
see in a sec. This one is called synthetic pleasures costume and it's a really really
comfy fabric jumpsuit that has a print, an all-over print. So really from head to toe.
And the good thing about this print and I've not seen anyone but Badinka doing it in this
perfection is that it doesn't fade when you wear it multiple times it doesn't
wash out and it doesn't get transparent when you stretch the fabric too much so
it's really really high quality print and I own several of these jumpsuits I
just love them because they look so good fun fact one of the suits I own I love
to wear for breakfast at festivals because it's just really comfy and it's
fun especially if you have the one with the eyes as I do. I'm going to show you
pictures so everyone is creeped out by you sitting at the breakfast table like that.
Anyway it's also really long enough so I can put my thumbs through the thumb holes
and do not have pain in my hands which is unusual but also really cool and also
the legs and arms and the torso are really long. So yeah this is basically my
favorite kind of cool non-fetishy jumpsuit brand. I can also close the zipper
of course and I love that there is like a contouring effect worked into the
overall bodysuit with the darker and lighter parts. And this is a perfect lazy
Halloween costume so to say because you can just put it on don't have to like
put too much effort into styling of course you can do a spacey makeup and
spacey hair with it but you can just wear it as it is and tip for cold
Halloween nights you can put tights underneath you can even put a really
fitting long sleeve underneath so you can dress it a bit warmer than the other
costumes anyway if you need a last-minute Halloween costume this is my
tip for you and this was my video for today so I hope you liked it leave a
comment and tell me which one of the costumes you like best give me a shout
if you already own Boudinka suits and are as happy with them as I am and
And I'll see you in the next video.
Have a happy Halloween and a nice time.
See ya.
Bye.